ILGWU. David Melman papers, 5780/152
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Maidenform, Incorporated: Fayetteville, North Carolina, Facility Correspondence, 1985-1996 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Maidenform, Incorporated: Master Agreement Correspondence [folder 1 of 2], 1969-1986 (Box 29, Folder 19)
- Maidenform, Incorporated: Master Agreement Correspondence [folder 2 of 2], 1969-1986 (Box 29, Folder 20)
- ILGWU Convention 1992: Photography, 1991-1992 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- ILGWU Convention 1992: Jobs with Justice Rally (Box 30, Folder 2)
- ILGWU Convention 1992: Registration, 1991-1992 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  Spanish
- ILGWU Convention 1992: Registration Forms (Box 30, Folder 4)
- ILGWU Convention 1992: Resolutions, 1989-1992 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- ILGWU Convention 1992: Retired Officers (Box 30, Folder 6)
- ILGWU Convention 1992: Schedule (Box 30, Folder 7)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Committee Report (Box 30, Folder 8)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Sergeant at Arms, 1989-1992 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Signs (Box 30, Folder 10)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Speakers, 1991-1992 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- ILGWU 1989 Convention: Stage Directions (Box 30, Folder 12)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Staff, 1989-1992 (Box 30, Folder 13)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Suggestions (Box 30, Folder 14)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Suites (Box 30, Folder 15)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Thank You Letters (Box 30, Folder 16)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Convention Themes, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 17)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Tips (Box 30, Folder 18)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Translation, Junk Mail, 1989-1994 (Box 30, Folder 19)
- PTL Free-Lance Translating Services and Associates: Contract, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 20)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Translation (Box 30, Folder 21)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Trips, 1990-1992 (Box 30, Folder 22)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Truck (Box 30, Folder 23)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Union Label Exhibit (Box 30, Folder 24)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: General Executive Board Report (Box 30, Folder 25)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Delegates Guide (Box 30, Folder 26)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Amendments, Resolution (Box 30, Folder 27)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Song Book, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 28)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Video, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 29)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Vouchers (Box 30, Folder 30)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Workshops, 1989-1992 (Box 30, Folder 31)
- Major Market Negotiations, 1991-1994 (Box 30, Folder 32)
- Dalil Fashions, Incorporated: Divisions (Box 30, Folder 33)
- Bill Blass, Limited (Box 30, Folder 34)
- Junior Gallery Limited: Divisions (Box 30, Folder 35)
- Karin Stevens, Incorporated (Box 30, Folder 36)
- Task Force Negotiation, 1991-1994 (Box 30, Folder 37)
- Leslie Fay, Incorporated: Negotiations, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 38)
- Resigned Firms, 1991-1994 (Box 30, Folder 39)
- Country Miss, Incorporated, 1991-1994 (Box 30, Folder 40)
- Leslie Fay Companies, Incorporated, 1986-1994 (Box 30, Folder 41)
- Leslie Fay Companies, Incorporated: Campaign, Arbitration, 1991-1993 (Box 30, Folder 42)
- General Executive Board: Appeal Committee, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 43)
- General Executive Board: Education Committee, 1987-1992 (Box 30, Folder 44)
- General Executive Board: Executive Committee, 1984-1991 (Box 30, Folder 45)
- General Executive Board: Finance Board, 1985-1990 (Box 30, Folder 46)
- ILGWU: Investment Committee, 1984-1988 (Box 30, Folder 47)
- General Executive Board: Committee on Organizing, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 48)
- Personnel Review Committee, 1977-1990 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- General Executive Board: Retiree Service Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- ILGWU: 1710 Broadway, Incorporated, 1986-1988 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- ILGWU: Staff Retirement Committee, 1987-1993 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Union Health Center Committee, 1983-1989 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- General Executive Board: Union Sanatorium Association Committee, 1984-1990 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- General Executive Board: Unity House Committee, 1984-1989 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- General Executive Board: Workers Benefits Committee, 1986-1991 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Officers and Staff Invited to Selected General Executive Board Meetings, 1985-1988 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- General Executive Board: Old Committee Charts, 1983-1988 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- General Executive Board: Committee Charts, 1987-1988 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- General Executive Board: Minutes Before 1986 Convention, 1983-1986 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- General Executive Board: Meeting Minutes [folder 1 of 2], 1989-1992 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- General Executive Board: Meeting Minutes [folder 2 of 2], 1989-1992 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Major Market Negotiations: Ranking File Meetings, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 15)
- Major Market Negotiations: Memos, 1993-1994 (Box 31, Folder 16)
- Task Forces: Negotiations, 1993-1994 (Box 31, Folder 17)
- Major Market Negotiations: Chronology, 1993-1994 (Box 31, Folder 18)
- General Executive Board: Major Market Negotiations, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 19)
- Follow Up of General Executive Board Actions, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 20)
- Ontario District Council: Correspondence, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Ontario District Council: Draft ILGWU Material, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  Chinese
- Ontario District Council: Employers, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Ontario District Council: History, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Ontario District Council: Letters From Members, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Ontario District Council: Members, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Ontario District Council: Membership Lists, Staff Lists, 1989-1995 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Ontario District Council: Minutes, News Letters, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  Chinese, Spanish
- Organizing Growth Projects, 1995-1997 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- UNITE: Organizing, 1995-1998 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Organizing, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Occupational Safety and Health Administration, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Papale, Carmen, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Governor George E. Pataki, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 14)
- E. Howard Molisani Memorial, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Pauline Newman Memorial Services, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 16)
- Francis Perkins Movie, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 17)
- Policy, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Postal Uniforms, 1996-1997 (Box 32, Folder 19)
- Puerto Rico Elections, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 20)
- Record Project, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 21)
- Retiree Services, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 22)
- Rice, Florence, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 23)
- Eleanor Roosevelt Monument, 1993-1995 (Box 32, Folder 24)
- San Francisco Organizing, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 25)
- Sculpture, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 26)
- Union Square Sculpture: Invoices, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 27)
- Union Square Sculpture: Contracts (signed), 1990 (Box 32, Folder 28)
- Seafarers, 1958-1988 (Box 32, Folder 29)
- Artist's Proposals, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 30)
- Sculpture Material, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 31)
- Task Force: Benefit Fund Provision, 1987-1988 (Box 32, Folder 32)
- Special Committee on Data Processing, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 33)
- Education Task Force: Subcommittee on Overview, Inventory and Fundraising, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 34)
- Education Task Force: Subcommittee on Servicing, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 35)
- Educational Task Force: Service Sub-Committee on Staff Training, Final Report, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 36)
- Special Committee on Health Service Plan, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Task Force: Item 807, 1982-1986 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Task Force: Committee on Local Structure, 1988-1989 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Special Committee on National Retirement Fund, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Strategic Analysis Working Group, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Task Force on Organization and New Directions, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Task Force on Social Services, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Task Force: Union Label Committee, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Task Force on Vacation and Holiday Provisions, 1985-1988 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Anne Klein Clippings, 1990-1991 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Crystal Brands: Clippings, 1984-1994 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- R&M Kaufman: Clippings, 1990-1991 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- TJX Company, Incorporated: Clippings, 1988-1992 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Task Force on Associate Membership, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: ASTWU (Box 34, Folder 1)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: AIM (Box 34, Folder 2)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Anthem (Box 34, Folder 3)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Badge (Box 34, Folder 4)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Bags (Box 34, Folder 5)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Blumberg Communications, Incorporated (Box 34, Folder 6)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Bedrooms, Suites, 1994-1995 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Bingo (Box 34, Folder 8)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Blumberg Communications (Box 34, Folder 9)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Blumberg Associates, 1992-1995 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Booths, 1986-1995 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Car Rentals, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Cars (Box 34, Folder 13)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Child Care (Box 34, Folder 14)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Chorus, 1992-1995 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Clergy and Greeters (Box 34, Folder 16)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Committees (Box 34, Folder 17)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Computers (Box 34, Folder 18)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Congratulations (Box 34, Folder 19)
- The Leslie Fay Companies, Calvin Klein Industries, 1994-1997 (Box 34, Folder 20)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Contracts (Box 34, Folder 21)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Convention Hall (Box 34, Folder 22)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Credentials, 1992-1995 (Box 34, Folder 23)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: David Melman, Invitations (Box 34, Folder 24)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Delegates (Box 34, Folder 25)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Delegates Guide (Box 34, Folder 26)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Election Notices, 1991-1995 (Box 34, Folder 27)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Fontainebleau Contracts (Box 34, Folder 28)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Fontainebleau Correspondence, 1992-1995 (Box 34, Folder 29)
- Fontainebleau Correspondence, 1992-1998 (Box 34, Folder 30)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Fraternal Greetings (Box 34, Folder 31)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: General Executive Board Report, 1992-1995 (Box 34, Folder 32)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Guests, 1989-1995 (Box 34, Folder 33)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: ILGWU Finale (Box 34, Folder 34)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Interpreters (Box 34, Folder 35)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Solomon, Irwin (Box 34, Folder 36)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Mazur, Jay (Box 34, Folder 37)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Letters to Delegates (Box 34, Folder 38)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Letters From ILGWU to Affiliates, 1992-1995 (Box 34, Folder 39)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Escort Committees (Box 34, Folder 40)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Little Book (Box 35, Folder 1)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Meeting Rooms (Box 35, Folder 2)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Merger and Constitution Committee (Box 35, Folder 3)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Merger Conference (Box 35, Folder 4)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Music, 1994-1995 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Officer Elections (Box 35, Folder 6)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Offices (Box 35, Folder 7)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Organizing Convention Committee (Box 35, Folder 8)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Outside Vendors (Box 35, Folder 9)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Parties (Box 35, Folder 10)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Photography (Box 35, Folder 11)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Posters (Box 35, Folder 12)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Printing (Box 35, Folder 13)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Proceedings (Box 35, Folder 14)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Proposals for Vendors, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 15)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Publications (Box 35, Folder 16)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Resolutions (Box 35, Folder 17)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Retirees (Box 35, Folder 18)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Schedule (Box 35, Folder 19)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Convention Schedule (Box 35, Folder 20)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Secretarial Pool (Box 35, Folder 21)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Sho-aids (Box 35, Folder 22)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Sho-Aids Bill (Box 35, Folder 23)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Signs (Box 35, Folder 24)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Site Visit, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 25)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Speakers, Acitce (Box 35, Folder 26)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Speakers Background, 1994-1995 (Box 35, Folder 27)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Speakers Biography (Box 35, Folder 28)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Staff Meetings (Box 35, Folder 29)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Stenographers, 1994-1995 (Box 35, Folder 30)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Suites, 1994-1996 (Box 35, Folder 31)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Suites, Catering (Box 35, Folder 32)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Theme, 1994-1995 (Box 35, Folder 33)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Truck (Box 35, Folder 34)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Vendors (Box 35, Folder 35)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Video ILGWU Commercial (Box 35, Folder 36)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Warehouse Organizer (Box 35, Folder 37)
- ILGWU Convention 1995: Workshops (Box 35, Folder 38)
- ACTWU, 1990-1998 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Activist Network (Box 36, Folder 2)
- ACTWU: Association Agreements, 1991-1995 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- ACTWU: Benefit Funds, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- ACTWU: Convention Booklets, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- ACTWU: Industry Structure, 1994-1995 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO Convention, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- AFL-CIO Convention, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- AFL-CIO Convention, 1978-1995 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- AFL-CIO Meetings, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- ALF-CIO: New York City Central Labor Council, 1996-1998 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- AFL-CIO: Ohio, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- AFL-CIO, 1995-1997 (Box 36, Folder 13)
- AFL-CIO: Union Solidarity, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 14)
- AFL-CIO: Executive Council Committees, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 15)
- AFL-CIO: Connecticut State AFL-CIO, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- AFL-CIO: Executive Council, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- ILGWU Research Department: Consumer Price Index, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 18)
- Collections, 1996-1998 (Box 36, Folder 19)
- Collection Control Department, 1996-1997 (Box 36, Folder 20)
- Data Processing Committee, 1992-1995 (Box 36, Folder 21)
- Drug Testing, 1986-1992 (Box 36, Folder 22)
- Dunlop Commission, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 23)
- Duke, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 24)
- Engineering Department, 1995-1997 (Box 36, Folder 25)
- Amalgamated Bank Literature, 1996-1998 (Box 36, Folder 26)
- Cost of Living Adjustment: Master Agreement, 1980-1981 (Box 36, Folder 27)
- Bobbie Brooks, Incorporated: Arbitration, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 28)
- Clinton Administration, 1992-1993 (Box 36, Folder 29)
- Clothing Manufacturers Association, 1995-1998 (Box 36, Folder 30)
- Code of Conduct, 1994-1997 (Box 36, Folder 31)
- Audix (Box 36, Folder 32)
- New York State Lobbying, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 33)
- The New Stagecraft Company, 1993-1994 (Box 36, Folder 34)
- Major Market Negotiations Task Force, 1987-1988 (Box 36, Folder 35)
- Task Force: Letters, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Major Market Negotiations, 1985-1988 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Negotiations, 1985-1988 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Negotiations: Settlements and Demands, 1985-1990 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Major Market Demands, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Major Market: Memorandums of Agreement, 1988-1991 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Major Market: Association List, 1988-1989 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Major Market Negotiations: Correspondence, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Major Market Demands, 1988-1991 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Major Market Negotiations: Early Preparations, 1988-1991 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Major Market Letters to Members, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Major Market Negotiations: Benefit Fund Rates, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Major Market: Press Coverage, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Major Market Negotiations: Summary Terms of Agreement, 1991-1994 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Benefits Task Force, 1990-1991 (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Communications Task Force, 1990-1991 (Box 37, Folder 16)
- Contract Language Task Force, 1990-1991 (Box 37, Folder 17)
- Seniority/Work Sharing Task Force, 1990-1991 (Box 37, Folder 18)
- Strike Preparations Task Force, 1990-1991 (Box 37, Folder 19)
- Warehouse Task Force, 1990-1991 (Box 37, Folder 20)
- Major Market Negotiations, 1991-1994 (Box 37, Folder 21)
- Section 936, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 22)
- Service Employees International Union, 1992-1993 (Box 37, Folder 23)
- 7th Avenue Exhibit, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 24)
- Sheinkman, Jack, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 25)
- Silvermoon Press, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 26)
- Solomon, Irwin, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 27)
- Southwest Region Leadership Institute, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 28)
- Strahs, Steve, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 29)
- Major Market Negotiations: Task Force Reports, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 30)
- Marriott At Glenpointe Hotel, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 31)
- Meeting Planning, 1988-1992 (Box 37, Folder 32)
- Minimum Wage Article, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 33)
- Midwest District Council #1, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 34)
- DOL: Model Agreement, 1993-1994 (Box 37, Folder 35)
- New England Collections, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 36)
- New England Project, 1995-1997 (Box 37, Folder 37)
- New Jersey, 1990-1994 (Box 37, Folder 38)
- NUFIS, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 39)
- NYCOSH Awards, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 40)
- NYCOSH, 1996-1999 (Box 37, Folder 41)
- New York Women's Apparel Industry Task Force, 1998-1999 (Box 37, Folder 42)
- Oberlin Winter Term, 1986-1988 (Box 37, Folder 43)
- Oberlin Winter Term, 1989-1991 (Box 37, Folder 44)
- 1989 Elections, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- 1988 Negotiations [folder 1 of 2], 1985-1988 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- 1988 Negotiations [folder 2 of 2] (Box 38, Folder 3)
- 1989 Convention J/R [folder 1 of 3], 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- 1989 Convention J/R [folder 2 of 3], 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- 1989 Convention J/R [folder 3 of 3] (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Stage Announcements (Box 39, Folder 1)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: AIM (Box 39, Folder 2)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Air Travel, 1991-1992 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Alternates, 1989-1991 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Archives Exhibit (Box 39, Folder 5)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Announcements (Box 39, Folder 6)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: A.V. Rentals, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Badges, 1991-1992 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Bags (Box 39, Folder 9)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Banquet, 1989-1992 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Bedrooms (Box 39, Folder 11)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Convention Bills (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Gelco Convention Services: Bill, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Bingo (Box 39, Folder 14)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Boat Ride (Box 39, Folder 15)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Boat Ride (Junk Mail), 1989 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Booths, 1991-1992 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Buses, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 18)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Catering, Suites, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 19)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Cars, 1991-1992 (Box 39, Folder 20)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Convention and Group Travel Association Correspondence, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 21)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Child Care (Box 39, Folder 22)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Chorus, 1989-1992 (Box 39, Folder 23)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Clergy/Greeters, 1989-1992 (Box 39, Folder 24)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Clippings (Box 39, Folder 25)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Convention Committees [Folder 1 of 2] (Box 39, Folder 26)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Convention Committees [Folder 2 of 2] (Box 39, Folder 27)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Computers, 1991-1992 (Box 39, Folder 28)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: ILGWU Constitution, 1991-1993 (Box 39, Folder 29)
- Spanish Constitution, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 30)
- Contracts, 1989-1992 (Box 39, Folder 31)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Contracts, 1989-1992 (Box 39, Folder 32)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Convention Daily, 1991-1992 (Box 39, Folder 33)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Chorus (Box 39, Folder 34)
- Delegate Certificates, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 35)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Credit Arrangements (Box 39, Folder 36)
- Communication Workers of America, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 37)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Dues, 1991-1992 (Box 39, Folder 38)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Edlen Electric (Box 39, Folder 39)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Elections, 1988-1992 (Box 39, Folder 40)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Election Appeals (Box 39, Folder 41)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Election Notices, January (Box 39, Folder 42)
- ILGWU Nomination, Election Meetings, 1988-1989 (Box 39, Folder 43)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Election Returns, Numerical, 1991-1992 (Box 39, Folder 44)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Convention Hall, 1991-1992 (Box 39, Folder 45)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Election Problems Resolved, 1991-1992 (Box 39, Folder 46)
- November Election Forms, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 47)
- 1991 Election Forms, December, 1991-1992 (Box 39, Folder 48)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Escort (Box 39, Folder 49)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Expenses (Box 39, Folder 50)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Fontainebleau Hilton Brochures (Box 39, Folder 51)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention (Box 39, Folder 52)
- Fontainebleau Correspondence [Folder 1 of 2], 1989-1992 (Box 39, Folder 53)
- Fontainebleau Correspondence [Folder 2 of 2], 1989-1992 (Box 39, Folder 54)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Fraternal Greetings (Box 39, Folder 55)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Fontainebleau Contract, 1989-1992 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Fontainbleau Contract Draft, 1989-1992 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: General Executive Board Report to the Convention, 1991-1992 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Gelco Convention Services, 1991-1992 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Gelco Contract (Box 40, Folder 5)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Guests, Florida (Box 40, Folder 6)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Mazur, Jay (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Guest Lists, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Convention Guide, 1989-1992 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Letters to Affiliates, 1989-1992 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Little Book (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Mazur, Jay, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Meetings, 1991-1992 (Box 40, Folder 13)
- Melman, David: Invitations, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 14)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Offices, 1989-1992 (Box 40, Folder 15)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Offices Chart (Box 40, Folder 16)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Office Equipment, 1991-1992 (Box 40, Folder 17)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Overview, 1988-1992 (Box 40, Folder 18)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Parties, 1990-1992 (Box 40, Folder 19)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Per Diem (Box 40, Folder 20)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Phone (Box 40, Folder 21)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Policy Statements (Box 40, Folder 22)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Printing, 1986-1992 (Box 40, Folder 23)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Press Coverage (Box 40, Folder 24)
- ILGWU 1992 Convention: Production Associates, 1991-1992 (Box 40, Folder 25)
- Zayre Corporation: Financial Information [folder 1 of 2], 1986-1988 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Zayre Corporation: Financial Information [folder 2 of 2], 1986-1988 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Recent Arbitrations, 1985-1992 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Leslie Fay Company: Master Agreement Correspondence, 1983-1986 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Leslie Fay Company: Master Agreement, Correspondence, 1973-1982 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Calvin Klein Industries: Good, Joe file [folder 1 of 3], 1979-1990 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Calvin Klein Industries: Good, Joe file [folder 2 of 3], 1979-1990 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Calvin Klein Industries: Good, Joe file [folder 3 of 3], 1979-1990 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Immigration Task Force: Mailing List, 1986-1987 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Immigration Articles, 1986-1987 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Homework, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Homework: Non-ILGWU Background Information, 1984-1987 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- September 16th Hearing, 1981-1986 (Box 41, Folder 13)
- Homework, 1986-1989 (Box 41, Folder 14)
- Homework, Bordeaux,Incorporated: Press Release Follow Up, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 15)
- Kamali Articles, 1980-1987 (Box 41, Folder 16)